Starting Phase 9B Validation Tests (Razorpay Integration)...

--- Test 1, 2, 3: Razorpay Generation & Manipulation Rejection ---
Buyer A creates payment intent: true
Razorpay TEST Order ID stored in PostgreSQL? true
Amount matches EXACT Order (Γé╣500.0) blocking injection? true

--- Test 5: Invalid Razorpay Signature ---
Safely blocked verifying payment? true

--- Test 6: Buyer A cannot verify Buyer B's payment ---
Strictly blocked Buyer B? (403) true

--- Test 8: Farmer blocked from accessing Buyer workflows ---
Farmer cleanly rejected (403) true

--- Test 4: Valid Signature Success State Transition ---
Valid signature accepted? true
PostgreSQL mutated to PAID? true

--- Test 7: Duplicate Re-Validation Protection ---
Blocked accurately duplicate execution (400)? true

--- Test 9: Orders untouched safely ---
Product deducted exactly (100 -> 90)? true

>>> ALL PHASE 9B TESTS PASSED: true
