Starting Phase 9A Validation Tests...

--- 1. Buyer A creates payment intent ---
Success? true
Status is strictly PENDING? true
Amount matches EXACT backend Order total (500) natively ignoring injection? true

--- 2. Prevent Duplicate Payment Simulation ---
Duplicate gracefully blocked (400)? true

--- 3. Buyer B tries to pay Buyer A's order ---
Blocked accurately (404/Not Found mappings)? true

--- 4. Farmer accesses payment API ---
Farmer blocked gracefully (403 Forbidden)? true

--- 5. Payment status persistent state extraction ---
Restores actively PENDING schema securely? true

>>> ALL TESTS PASSED: true
