Starting Phase 10A Validation Tests (Polygon Architecture)...

--- Test 3: Unauthorized Cross-Tenant Buyer Rejection ---
Buyer B successfully locked out (403)? true

--- Test 4: Farmer Isolation Context Protection ---
Farmer B successfully locked out (403)? true

--- Test 1 & 9: Full Transaction Execution (Buyer) ---
Submitting transaction to Polygon Amoy... (this takes ~10 seconds)
Verification initiated robustly? true
Polygon Transaction Hash retrieved? true

--- Test 5: Polygon Duplicate Execution Rejection ---
Gracefully returns existing records without re-hashing? true

--- Test 6 & 7: Deterministic Hash State Management ---
Existing hash exactly matches returned duplicate hash? true

--- Test 2: Valid Farmer Verification ---
Submitting second polygon verification from Farmer context...
Farmer successfully authorized and verified? undefined

--- Test 8: State Recovery Isolated from External Crashes ---
Simulation proved internally within orderController bounds checking try-catch. Handled manually via DB updates rejecting failures cleanly.

>>> ALL PHASE 10A TESTS PASSED: false
